And we're going to go through three phases of this drill that's going to warm up your body and also work on your coordination and agility.
I'll take it through half speed first and then my partner Jonesy is going to take it full speed through so you really get an idea of the intensity and how the warm-up should be applied before the workout.
So the first phase is bilateral using two legs at the same time.
Start on the side, the far side of the rectangle.
Jump at the same time to the center, land on your toes, jump further across, land on your toes, then return back to center.
Return back across.
So forward, forward, nice and fluid and back.
The second phase is both feet together on one corner.
Saw them across center, saw them across front then across the front, other side, then back to center, then back and across.
So again, it?s one, two, three, four, five, six.
Then the last phase is one leg at a time.
I'm going to start with my right.
One, two, across the top, back to center and then switch the feet.
One, two, three and now Jonesy's going to take the whole entire routine and do it full speed for you.
So Jonesy's going to take it full speed here.
What we're trying to do is we're trying to balance working as fast as we can with accuracy, ok?
So Jonesy, whenever you're ready.
He's going to take it both feet first, he's working as fast as he can and as accurate as he can.
We do it three times with that phase, then we'll move on to the next phase.
We'll work that three times through.
Again, still working as fast as you can, but as accurate as you can.
Then once you're done with three times that way, then we're going to bring it over to the one foot and again, working as fast as you can as accurate as you can too.
Then switch feet.
Three times through for each foot.
And there, you should be ready to go, nice and warmed up.